莱纳德  我们在伯克利分校教课的开场笑话
Leonard, I've been working on an opening joke
我费了不少功夫准备
for our lecture at Berkeley.
我是挺喜欢笑
Oh, I like to laugh.
不过你想说就说吧
But say it anyway.
好吧
Okay, um...
你该跟伯克利分校的
What do you say to a graduate
物理系毕业生说什么呢
of the UC Berkeley physics department?
我点的餐要配薯条
I'll have fries with that.
因为他们接受的教育不足以
Because his education hasn't prepared him
让他们在科学领域找到工作
for a career in the sciences.
等学生们冲过来打你们时
You know, when they chase you out of there,
你只要跑得比谢尔顿快就没事了
you only have to run faster than Sheldon.
出发都做好准备了吗
Are you all set for your trip?
应该吧
Yeah, I think so.
我重新帮共所包补了货
I just restocked the old PRK.
什么"共所包"
"P.R.K"?
公共厕所用品包
Public restroom kit.
内含一名小男孩要在陌生新环境嘘嘘
Everything a boy needs for making pee pee
所需要的一切用品
in new and strange places.
带着个背包放自己的厕纸和干洗手液
I don't see what's crazy about bringing a backpack
有什么值得奇怪的啊
with your own toilet paper and Purell.
接着说
Keep going.
还有橡胶手套  空气清新剂
And rubber gloves, uh, air freshener.
抗噪耳机
Um, noise-cancelling headphones.
防狼警笛
Oh, danger whistle.
防狼喷雾
pepper spray.
多语言版"已占用"的牌子
Ooh, a multi-language "Occupied" sign.
我看看
Uh, let's see.
还有马桶坐垫纸  鞋套
We have seat protectors, uh, booties for my shoes,
夹鼻子的晒衣夹
a clothespin for my nose.
还有连棍子的镜子
Oh, and a mirror on a stick,
这样我可以确保隔壁厕间的人
so I can make sure the person in the stall next to me
不是什么变态之类的
isn't some kind of weirdo.
你还担心伯克利分校会有姑娘
You still worried some Berkeley girl
把他抢走吗
is gonna steal him away?
当然  不然你觉得他的防狼警笛是谁给的
Yes, who do you think gave him the danger whistle?
你要玩我发明的物理学车上游戏吗
Would you like to play a physics car game I invented
名字叫"我是没用间谍"
called "I Can't Spy"?
保留了"我是小间谍"紧张刺激的部分
It's all the nail-biting tension of "I Spy"
但是加入了有趣的亚原子粒子
but the added fun of subatomic particles
与儿童玩的车上游戏  出题者选定一件看到的事物
说出指定对白  并提示该事物首字母给对方猜
与可见光谱外的光波
and waves outside the visible spectrum.
如果这游戏有
If it's half as much fun as
"1乘10的4次方瓶啤酒在墙上"那么好玩
"One Times Ten to the Fourth Bottles of Beer on the Wall,"
99瓶啤酒在墙上也是常见车上游戏
反复唱着歌词  每次往下减一  直到墙上没了
我就玩
I'm in.
我先开始
I'll begin.
小间谍我的眼睛不能看到...
Uh, I can't spy with my little eye...
某个直接穿过我们的东西
something passing right through us.
我刚才喝的大豆星冰乐
That soy Frappuccino I had.
还能不能好好玩游戏了
Will you please play the game?
小间谍我的眼睛不能看到...
I can't spy with my little eye
某个直接穿过我们的东西
something passing right through us.
我不知道啊
I don't know, um...
如果每秒有650亿太阳中微子
If 65 billion solar neutrinos pass
通过每平方厘米的区域
through a square centimeter every second,
按照我们这车的表面积来算
given the surface area of this car is
也就大概6万平方厘米吧
about 60,000 square centimeters,
所以通过的太阳中微子大概有3900兆那么多吗
that means 3.9 times ten to the 15th solar neutrinos?
我不想玩了
I don't want to play anymore.
我们好久没有一起自驾游了
We haven't been on a road trip in a while.
还挺好玩的
This is fun.
知道你赢了好吗
We get it-- you won the game.
不用这么臭显摆吧
Stop bragging.
不是啦  我们一起写了篇论文
No, listen, we wrote a paper together.
现在还要一起去大学做论文的演讲
Now we get to go to a university and talk about it?
这蛮酷的不是吗
That's pretty cool.
我想是吧
I suppose it is.
其实  如果你想要放点音乐来庆祝一下
In fact, if you'd like to celebrate with a little music,
我不会介意哦
I'd be okay with that.
虾米
What...?
这趟自驾游要疯狂啦
This road trip just got crazy.
放那放克乐吧  白人男孩
Play that funky music, white boy.
我真没想到你知道这个哏
I'm surprised you know that reference.
什么哏
What reference?
我把所有要卖的东西上都贴了贴纸
So, I put stickers on everything we're gonna sell.
大家帮忙搬出去到车道上就行了
We just need help taking it all out to the driveway.
能让我来负责价格吗
Can I be in charge of pricing?
我这辈子去过无数车库拍卖
I've been going to garage sales my whole life.
你们相信这条连裤袜我只花了5分钱就买到吗
Can you believe I got these pantyhose for a nickel?
行  艾米负责价钱
All right, Amy's in charge of pricing
以及当75岁老人
and being 75.
佩妮  能帮忙搭把手吗
Hey, Penny, can you give me a hand with this?
行
Sure.
我小时候家里也有这个
Aw, we had one of these growing up.
我以前天天玩
I used to play all the time.
是吗  我也爱打乒乓球
Oh, yeah? I love Ping-Pong.
我说的是啤酒乒乓[饮酒游戏]
Oh, I meant beer pong.
我家也有球桌
I had a table, too,
可是我以前没有朋友
but I didn't have any friends,
所以我只能一直发球
so all I did was serve.
你可以半边桌不要平放下来  跟桌面对打啊
You know, you can leave one side up and play against it.
如果当年我有朋友  或许就会有人教我这事
And if I had a friend, they might have told me that.
抱歉
Excuse me.
为什么这上面会有要卖的标签
Why is there a sticker on this?
这是我的《神秘博士》塔迪斯
It's my TARDIS from Doctor Who.
《神秘博士》中的电话亭外观时光机
内部空间比外面大许多
我本来准备把它移进家里的
I was planning on moving it in the house.
你的话已经回答了你的问题
I think you just answered your own question.
干嘛这样  说不定某天它价格会翻倍
Come on, one day, this may double in value
能达到我当时买价的一半
and be worth half what I paid for it.
亲爱的  我们的事情还很多
Sweetie, we have a lot to do.
我们不需要现在就决定这个
We don't need to decide this right now.
只要你能有一颗包容的心  我没意见
Well, I guess as long as you're keeping an open mind.
当然啦
Of course.
* 放那放克乐  白人男孩 *
* Play that funky music, white boy *
* 放对那放克乐 *
* Play that funky music right *
* 放那放克乐  白人男孩 *
* Play that funky music, white boy *
所以他们要求
So... they're requesting
那个白人男孩放那放克乐对吧
that the white boy play the funky music, yes?
是啊
Yes.
而我们现在在听的歌
And this music we're listening to right now
就是放克乐  对吧
is funky as well?
是啊
Sure.
我问你个问题
Let me ask you this.
你觉得这首歌
Do you think
是不是那个白人男孩去放的那首放克乐
this song is the music the white boy ultimately play?
有可能啊
It could be.
所以这就是像是音乐界的罗素悖论
So it's like the musical equivalent of Russell's Paradox,
所有不包含自身的集合
the question of whether the set of all sets
本身是否属于该集合
that don't contain themselves as members contains itself?
-没错  -这样的话
- Exactly. - Well...
我讨厌这首歌
then I hate it.
音乐就应该是纯娱乐
Music should just be fun.
基本没浪费时间
Making great time.
我们会很早到那里
Gonna be there pretty early.
我们的酒店房间会准备好了吗
Will our hotel room be ready?
难说
I doubt it.
你不担心如果我们在大堂
Aren't you worried that sitting in the lobby
坐得时间太久
for a long period of time
会引起酒店侦探的注意吗
might attract the attention of the hotel detective?
如果真引起注意
If we do,
我们就叫他"好狗不挡路  滚"
we'll just tell him to "hit the bricks, see?"
感觉有点太霸气了  不过行吧
Seems a little confrontational, but all right.
我们现在这里离天行者牧场不远
You know, we won't be very far from Skywalker Ranch.
乔治·卢卡斯花费一亿美元买下的
16平方公里地  用作电影拍摄与工作场所
这倒是
Oh, that's true.
我们又不能进去
It's not like we can get in there.
为什么不能
Why not?
乔治·卢卡斯把他的总部
I-I don't think George Lucas put his headquarters
设在荒郊野外
in the middle of nowhere
就是为了不想有人乱入
because he wanted people dropping in.
星战里尤达大师的沼泽也是在荒郊野外啊
Yoda's swamp was in the middle of nowhere.
星战里  天行者的故乡也是荒郊野外啊
Tatooine was in the middle of nowhere.
霍思星  也是偏僻到不行啊
Hoth was in the middle of nowhere.
这是暗号  莱纳德
That's code, Leonard.
他希望我们乱入
He wants us to drop in.
我们是还有多余时间
We do have time.
我们可以开车经过看一下
I mean, we could drive by and just look at it.
太好了
Yes! Oh...
我好兴奋
I'm so excited.
藏都藏不住
And I just can't hide it.
"我就快要失控  而我喜欢这感觉"
"I'm about to lose control, and I think I like it."
以上几句全是来自指针姐妹合唱团歌曲
《I'm so excited》的歌词
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
你们两个打算什么时候搬进来呢
So when do you guys think you're gonna move in?
我们还在考虑要装修哪里
We're still figuring how much remodeling we want to do.
要在"有品位现代化"
It's tricky finding the right balance between
与"犹太老妈俗气破烂"之间找平衡挺有难度
"Tasteful modern" and "Jewish mother tchotchke crapfest."
你们决定好怎么处置塔迪斯了吗
Have you made a decision about the TARDIS?
换个名字我应该能卖掉
I think I can sell it if we call it,
叫"大号英式移动公厕"
"Big British Porta-Potty."
我们不卖  这是我的东西
We're not selling it-- it's mine.
你不能随便做决定
You can't just decide.
不然我们比腕力定胜负吧
How about I arm-wrestle you?
这不公平啊
That's not fair.
这就跟我用性感裤子比赛虐你一样
It's like me challenging you to a sexy pants contest.
你们可以打乒乓定输赢啊
You could play Ping-Pong for it.
这我可以接受
I would do that.
这怎么就公平了
How is that fair?
你从小家里就有球桌
You grew up with a table.
但我几乎都是用来当做
Yes, but I mostly used it as a battlefield
变形金刚与霹雳猫之间的战场  让他们争夺
in an ongoing war between the Transformers and the ThunderCats
我在树林捡来的胸罩的控制权
for control of a bra I had found in the woods.
伯纳黛特  看在莱纳德逼我
Bernadette, for every episode of Doctor Who
看过的所有《神秘博士》的仇
Leonard has made me sit through,
我愿意为你出战
I will play on your behalf
把塔迪斯送回加利弗雷去
and send that TARDIS back to Gallifrey,
我真恨我还知道了它母星叫什么
where I hate that I know it belongs.
行  佩妮替我出赛
Yes, Penny plays for me.
这不公平啊  她有上半身肌肉
That's not fair-- she has upper body muscles.
兄弟  我可是三届
Dude, three-time Sanskriti School
印度含金汤匙小孩学校的羽毛球冠军
for Well-Born Boys badminton champion.
对啊  行  拉杰替我出赛
That's right-- okay, Raj can play for me.
你们都选厉害的人代打
Ooh, you just chose champions.
感觉像是在重演旧时德国的
It's like we're reenacting the ancient German practice
-决斗裁判法  -是啊  就像是
- of trial by combat. - Yeah, it's also like
《权利的游戏》里魔山大战红毒蛇那样
when the Mountain fought the Red Viper in Game of Thrones.
也是莱纳德逼你看的吧
Leonard makes you watch that, too?
没  我挺喜欢这剧
No, no, I like that show.
里面有龙  还有人做爱
It's got dragons and people doing it.
就这么定了
So it's settled.
《神秘博士》的塔迪斯的去留
The fate of Doctor Who's TARDIS will be decided
将由在霹雳猫大战变形金刚的旧战场上
by a Game of Thrones inspired death-match on the battlefield
由一场受《权利的游戏》启发的死斗来决定
of ThunderCats versus Transformers.
如果当年那个胸罩还在  我出5分钱跟你买
If you still have that bra, I'll give you a nickel for it.
到了
There it is.
只有个闸门
It's just a gate.
在路中间
On a road.
而且一点也不难找
Wasn't even that hard to find.
这也太赞了
This is so amazing!
对啊
I know!
想去拍个照吗
You want to get a picture?
我不只想要照片
I want more than a picture.
我想进去
I want to go in.
我也想进去  不过他们肯定不让进
Well, so do I, but they'll never let us.
你泡到佩妮靠的是这态度吗
Is that the attitude that helped you get Penny?
不是啊  可是我也没有三年时间
No, but I don't have three years
可以让那个闸门同情我啊
to make that gate feel sorry for me.
那边有个对讲机
Uh, there's a speaker box.
开过去  按按钮
Drive up, push the button,
看看会发生什么事
and let's see what happens.
好吧
Okay, yeah.
按一下又不会少块肉
What do we have to lose?
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous.
克服它
Well, get over it.
这种情况最需要的就是自信
Confidence is key in these situations.
是的
Right.
你还真按了  你疯了吗
You pushed it-- are you out of your mind?!
有事能帮忙吗
May I help you?
我们没有预约
Uh, uh... we don't have an appointment,
也不应该来这里
and-and we don't belong here,
但我们是超级疯狂粉
but we-we're, like, crazy-big fans.
我是指
I mean...
"对星战很疯狂"的狂热粉
"Crazy for Star Wars" crazy,
不是那种有一背包绑架胶带的疯狂
not crazy like we have a backpack full of duct tape,
不过我们的确是有个背包
although we do have a backpack
里面装满了你不会想看的东西
that you really don't want to look in.
你要搞砸了
You're blowing it.
我们想见乔治·卢卡斯
We want to meet George Lucas
跟他当朋友  跟他一起玩
and become his friends and play with him!
有人吗
Hello?
这对讲机失灵了  你们就开进来吧
This speaker's not working, just pull up.
就是这么整
And that's how it's done.
好了  我们过了第一关
All right, we've defeated the first challenge.
我们现在得硬起来  对抗这个
Now we must steel ourselves to face the monster
镇守大门的怪兽
who defends the gate.
我们是要避开一个保安
We're trying to get past a security guard,
又不是拯救塞尔达[游戏名]
not rescue Zelda.
我看是你那吊儿郎当的念头才需要拯救吧
I think what really needs to be rescued is your sense of whimsy,
不过现在先解决这件事
but one quest at a time.
所以你的计划是什么
So what's the plan?
我决定对那个保安实话实说
Uh, I'm just gonna be honest with the guy.
说实话我们永远进不去
Honesty will never get us in.
那你的计划是什么
Well, what's your plan?
我的计划是预估一下
All right, my plan is predicated on the assumption
里面有医疗室的可能性
that they have a nurse's office
以及你同意被小捅一刀的自愿度
and your willingness to be lightly stabbed.
你们要去拜访谁
Who are you here to see?
我还是实话实说吧
Uh, I'm just gonna tell you the truth.
真是要了亲命了
Oh, you are killing me.
我们没有预约
We don't have an appointment.
我们是卢卡斯先生的忠实粉丝
We-we're just fans of Mr. Lucas's work,
我们只想来碰碰运气
and we thought we'd take a shot
您能不能让我们进去看看
and see if we could get in and look around.
抱歉各位  这种人我们见多了
Sorry, guys, we get this a lot.
我不能让你们进去
Can't let you in.
如果我告诉你我就是尤达的配音呢
What if I told you that I was the voice of Yoda?
我必须进去参加一场配音会议
A recording session I must attend.
对不起  别理他
I'm sorry, don't listen to him.
我们其实是物理学家
We're actually physicists.
我们一会儿要去伯克利分校上课
We're giving a lecture at Berkeley later today.
我们只是想消磨一下时间
We just... we had some time to kill.
我说  你们看上去也是体面的人
Hey, listen, you seem like decent guys.
我不能让你们进去
I can't let you in,
但我可以送你们一些帽子和纪念T恤
but I got some hats and T-shirts I can give you.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
看到没
See?
诚实才是最宝贵的...
Maybe honesty is the best...
你在干什么呢
What are you doing?
当然是挣脱那束缚我的枷锁
Shedding the yoke of my oppressors,
你这个无知  可悲的小矮子
you blind, sad little man.
不许动
Don't move!
代号AA23  AA23
Code A-A-23, A-A-23.
收到
Copy.
我看到牧场了  莱纳德
I can see the ranch, Leonard!
充满了乡村气息  真美啊
Oh, it's rustic, it's lovely.
我想拍个照片  可是好多人在追我
I'd take a picture, but people are chasing me.
我就要成功了
I'm gonna make it...!
I'm gonna make it!
他们有脉冲电击枪  可他们肯定不敢...
They have Tasers, but they wouldn't dare use...
拉杰  加油
Come on, Raj.
你是乒乓届的金刚
You are the King Kong of Ping-Pong.
你是桌球届的霸王
You are the menace of table tennis.
赶紧灭了她  我想不出第三句了
Put her away, 'cause I don't have a third one.
太好了
Yes!
拉杰8分  佩妮4分
Rajesh eight, Penny four.
抱歉  他实在是太强了
Sorry, he's really good.
拉杰
Hey, Raj.
如果霍华德不能留着塔迪斯
if Howard can't keep the TARDIS,
把它放在你家会不会很酷啊
how great would it look at your place?
什么
What?
对啊  什么
Yeah, what?
我对《神秘博士》了解不多
I don't know much about Doctor Who,
但是如果你把它放在大门外面
but if, um, you were to put this right outside your front door
再把后门跟你家大门打开
and open up the back,
你的整个公寓就仿佛
it would be like your entire apartment was
变成了塔迪斯的内部
the inside of the TARDIS,
很酷对不对
which is pretty cool
因为在电视剧里  时间机器的内部
'cause on the show, the inside of the TARDIS
的确比外观大得多
is bigger than the outside.
但话说回来  我对《神秘博士》了解并不多
But then again, I don't know much about Doctor Who.
别听她的
Don't listen to her.
我俩交情似海深  兄弟如手足啊
You and I go way back-- we're like brothers.
没错  没错
We are. We are.
哎呀  人家发球太烂了
Oh, no! What a terrible serve!
抱歉了  手足
Sorry, brother.
-8比5  -这太无耻了
- Eight-five. - This is ridiculous.
我要换选手
I want a new champion.
艾米  你说你会发球是真的吗
Amy, were you serious about being able to serve?
那已经是很久以前的事了
Uh, it-it's been a long time.
我也没把握
I don't know.
我的技术可能都荒废了
I'm probably pretty rusty.
她才是我的新选手
She's my champion!
如果你可以换  我也可以
Well, if you can switch champions, so can I.
-我选拉杰  -喂
- I want Raj. - Hey.
拜托  好像你介意似的
Oh, come on, like you even care.
我是介意啊
I care!
等等  我才不介意呢  加油吧  拉杰
Oh, wait, no, I don't. Good luck, Raj.
我以为我们的友情对你来说更重要呢
You know, I thought our friendship meant more to you.
我也这么以为
So did I.
你觉得他们会通报警察吗
Do you think they're gonna call the police?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许他们会通报帝国警察
Maybe they'll call Imperial Officers to take us
然后把我们关进死星里的小牢房吧
to a holding cell on the Death Star.
帝国警察才不会屈尊来处理这种事呢
Oh, I think that's below the pay grade of an Imperial Officer.
暴风部队真正的职能是...
Stormtroopers are really the ones who...
闭嘴吧你
Oh, shut up.
他说得对
He's right.
暴风部队其实兼负了
Uh, Stormtroopers actually combine both the function
步兵和宪兵两种职能
of infantry and military police.
我这人一般挺和善的
Uh-huh, I'm normally very nice,
但你丫也给我闭嘴吧
but you shut up, too.
话说
So...
你是为什么进来的
what are you in for?
我只是想见见卢卡斯先生  向他致谢
Honestly, I just wanted to meet Mr. Lucas and say thank you.
这电影在我成长之路上意义重大
You know, growing up, the movies had such an impact on my life.
我这人在哪里都不合群
I never really fit in anywhere.
直到我发现了他创造的世界
Till I discovered the worlds he created
才终于找到了属于我的地方
and finally found a place where I belong.
但你怎么会在这里呢
But why are you here?
我...我翻过了栏杆
Oh, I, uh, I hopped a fence,
结果他们抓到我在雕像馆
and they caught me in the sculpture gallery
和一个楚巴卡雕塑亲热
making out with a Chewbacca statue.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
莱纳德
Leonard,
里面还有雕像馆呢
they have a sculpture gallery.
我跟我的上司汇报了
All right, I talked to my supervisor,
我们这次只给你们一个警告
and we're gonna let you go with a warning.
不过如果你们还敢来
But if you ever come back,
我们会报警并起诉你
we will call the police and press charges.
我们明白
We understand.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
那我呢
Uh, what about me?
你哪里也不能去  接吻狂魔
No, you're not going anywhere, kissy face.
来吧
Let's go.
我要给你们拍照贴在大门外
I have to take your picture to post at the guard gate.
关于照片我有个问题
Uh, one question about that picture.
我能跟乔治·卢卡斯一起拍吗
Can it be with George Lucas?
好凶巴巴哦
Ooh, grumpy you are.
好了  现在是最终对决
Okay, this is the match that decides it all.
先得十一分的人赢
First to 11 wins.
每五分换发一次
Serve switches every five points.
跟你说一声  本来一开始
And just so you know, when this started,
我只是想把塔迪斯放在房子不碍事的角落
I was going to put the TARDIS in a discreet corner of the house,
可是我现在生气了
but I've since turned mean,
所以我会把它摆在客厅的最中间
and now it's going right in the middle of the living room
或者放在转台上  并挂着"咬我啊"
on a rotating platform with a sign that says "Suck it".
比赛开始
Game on.
反正
Except...
拉杰会赢
Raj is gonna win.
是不是  拉杰
Isn't that right, Raj?
可是她发球发得不错
Uh, yeah, I mean, her serve was pretty good.
给点力啊  攻敌先攻心
Come on, get in her head.
气势上先压倒她
Be intimidating.
好吧
Okay, uh...
我会虐爆你的  贱人
I'm gonna own you, bitch!
太过分了
That's not nice.
我们还是开始吧
Let's just play.
一比零
One-zero.
二
Two.
三
Three.
四
Four.
五比零
Five-nothing.
等等  你以前打的是羽毛球
Wait, did you play badminton
还是羽毛糗
or sad-minton?
别听他的  她就只有发球好
Don't listen to him-- all she's got is a serve.
去换个新卫生棉条再来干掉她
Now, grab a fresh tampon and put her away.
啥
Wha...?
这话就不过分吗
A-And that's not offensive?
标准到底在哪
Where's the line?
在你的女用皮包里  赶紧打
It's in your purse. Play.
一比五
One-five.
二比五
Two-five.
三比五
Three-five.
四比五
Four-five.
五比五
Five-five!
六
Six.
七
Seven.
八
Eight.
九
Nine.
十比五
Ten-five!
六
Six.
七
Seven.
八
Eight.
九
Nine.
十比十
Ten-ten!
刚才那四十秒真是激动人心啊
Well, that was an exciting 40 seconds.
的确是  不过现在回到你发球了
It was, and now the serve is back to you,
游戏要结束了
and the game is over.
你知道吗  艾米  我
You know, Amy, I, uh...
我一直在想要是塔迪斯在你家
can't help but wonder how Sheldon would react
谢尔顿会有什么反应
if the TARDIS was at your place.
别听她的  快发球
Don't listen to her, just hit the ball.
继续说
Keep talking.
如果连这个都不能拐他进你闺房
If this doesn't get him into your bedroom,
也没有别的可以了
nothing will.
你还在生我气吗
Are you still mad at me?
对  我们没赶上演讲  差点被拘捕
Yes, we missed our lecture, we were almost arrested,
你还害我跟一个强行把舌头
and you got me locked in a room with a man
塞进伍基人玩偶喉咙里的男人关在一起
who forced his tongue down the throat of a stuffed Wookie.
杯子半空的悲观人儿啊
Boy, some people are just glass-half-empty.
杯子是全空的好吗  谢尔顿
The glass is empty, Sheldon.
完全是空的
It's completely empty.
如果你把那杯子给一个快要渴死的人
If you gave that glass to a man who was dying of thirst,
他就死定了  你知道为什么吗
he would be dead, do you know why?
我先问一下  他抽烟吗
Before I answer, was he a smoker?
我觉得你看待事情的角度不对
I think you're looking at this all wrong.
好吧  那你告诉我我应该怎么看待这件事
Fine, then tell me how I should be looking at it.
我们不仅到了天行者农场  还进到里面了
Well, not only did we go to Skywalker Ranch, we got in.
我们认识的人里没人做到过
And no one we know can say that.
而且你不是一直觉得我很烦人吗
And for all the times you find me irritating,
今天你终于可以有人电击我了
today you got to watch someone shoot me with a Taser.
这部分是不错
That part was pretty good.
是吧
See?
你被电到满地抽抽啊
You did flop around a lot.
这一点我承认
I'll take your word for it.
我当时正忙着不让自己尿出来
I was too busy trying not to defecate.
话说他们带我们去拘留室的时候
You know, when they were escorting us to the detaining room,
我看进一扇门
I looked through a door,
我很确定我看到了一个展示台
and I'm pretty sure I saw a display case
里面装着约柜[圣物]
with the Ark of the Covenant.
-太神奇了  -就是啊
- That's amazing. - I know.
我还看到赫特人贾巴骑着摩托车经过呢
And I saw Jabba the Hutt riding by on a motorcycle.
不过那时我刚被电过
Although that was right after the Tasing,
所以我也不确定是真是假
so who can say for sure?
我觉得我们这可以算是一场冒险
I-I guess this could count as an adventure.
确实是
It was.
而且虽然他们禁止我们再去
And even though we're not allowed back there,
但却夺不走我们今天的经历
they can never take today away from us.
但不包括我的嗅觉
Unlike my sense of smell,
被电击完到现在还没恢复呢
which hasn't returned since the Tasing.
不  什么都闻不到
No, I got nothing.
艾米  戴立克正追着我跑呢
Amy, the Daleks are right on my tail!
快  我们得回去重设时间线
Quick, we need to reset the time circuits.
不  我忘拿我的音速起子了
Oh, no, I left my sonic screwdriver behind.
我当时真应该好好考虑
Really should have thought this through.